Open and make a good flower model
The model must be placed on the origin
There is a floor in the 3D window
Two vertical lines on the floor
This focal point in the middle of the x-axis and y-axis
This place is the origin
This flower must be placed flat on the origin of the floor
Because the origin is the point where the button is pointed to the top of the board
Next, export the model to OPT
Name and then click Save
See this export window
Choose all panels
Here you must choose a single target
You don't care about merging or not
Choose the one after
Unified UV coordinates do not need to be selected
Because this flower itself has no texture
The flag color does not need to be saved
Choose the one after
And save the zip with the texture file
Is saved as a compression bag
The bottom one can not be selected
Because this flower itself is white
There is no texture
Click to confirm
Find a well-preserved compression bag
Unscrew
Add a button
Choose button
Find this plus sign
Next to it, press the symbol to connect
Connect with a lot of button material
Click the plus sign
On the left is the corresponding setting
On the right is the preview window
Then next
We need to add OPT first
Click the browse button
Click open
All of these grid
Here are only two grid
Easy to select
If at first
When you export OPT
The choice is not a single target
But more targets
Then this place
Select all
Select
Then this place
This flower will be separated into several flower spots
There will be dozens of flower spots
There will be dozens of grid
It's more complicated to go left, right and left
So when you go forward
Select one target is more convenient
See above here
You canzung your name
Just name
Airline
Now the view value is
야지
It «s better if you change the size
According to »,
Return to the нужно
For example, the width of my flower is reduced to 10
Then you change the thickness of the bottom to 4
That is, the width and thickness are kept in relative proportion
This can ensure that the flower will not deform
Set the width to 15 mm
Then the thickness should be 6.2
The following axis is converted, no need to operate anymore
At the beginning, when it was turned out to be OPT, the flower was placed at the origin
It is equivalent to aligning all the axis directions
No need to change anymore
Click to confirm
Use the option to move the twist tool
Select the front and middle twist
Appliance new twist
According to the material and color of the twist